SOME SCENES IN THE STORY TAKE PLACE IN
VARIOUS PARTS OF INDIA INCLUDING DELHI
BUT FOR THE CONVENIENCE OF THE VIEWERS,
THE CHARACTERS COMMUNICATE IN TELUGU.
Chennai Tower, this is Deccan Air 582.
Minimum fuel.
Requesting landing clearance.
Go around, Deccan Air 582.
Unable to go around.
I said we have a fuel emergency,
goddammit!
-I say again, Deccan Air 582--
-Why aren't you letting me land?
There's something wrong.
They are ignoring protocol.
-Requesting reason for denial!
-You are not cleared to land!
-Why aren't you letting him land?-Who are you? Call the guards!
Maha? Maha, what's going on there?
-Why aren't they permitting me to land?
-Che, Tambaram Air Force. Runway 1-5.
Land there!
Do you have enough fuel for that?
There's enough fuel to land there.
-You sure you want us to proceed?
-I'm sure.
-It will be a problem, Maha.
-Land at Tambaram!
-I'll handle it!
-Roger.
-Stop running.
-Che, come in.
Parade!
Attention!
Keep going!
Careful!
Come in Tambaram Ground Control.
This is Captain Chaitanya Rao,
batch of 1987.
Please acknowledge.
You don't have permission
to land here, Captain.
This is military territory.
Turn around immediately! It's an order!
Come in, Che!
Careful.
You're flying into restricted area.
It's dangerous!
Go. Go fast!
-Security breach at gate number one!
-Hey.
-Stop, stop.
-Stop the vehicle.
Shit, shit, shit.
Che, are you okay!
Can you hear me, Che?
SURIYA
Che?
PARESH RAWAL
APARNA BALAMURALI
URVASHI
KARUNAS
CO-STARRING
"PADMA SHRI" DR.MOHAN BABU.M
AAKAASAM NEE HADDHU RA!
[SKY IS YOUR LIMIT!]
How can you stuff yourself with meat
after a pilgrimage?
That chap's no longer in the army.
His relatives say he's unemployed.
Why are you so hell-bent on meeting him?
-What's the big deal?
-It's unprecedented.
It's unheard of for a girl's family
to visit a boy.
He refused to see you!
Why are you dying to see him?
Look, she's eating shamelessly!
He refused to treat me
like an animal for sale
that's why we're going.
She'll choose her husband
like Sita chose Lord Rama.
-Right, kiddo?
-Stop calling her kiddo.
You're spoiling this buffalo.
Stop taking her side.
Are you talking about me?
Am I really spoilt?
I'm the only one in the family
to clear 12th grade in one go.
You spent lakhs
to make this dimwit an engineer.
Don't drag me into this.
They are spending a fortune on you.
Shut her up, dad!
Listen girl,
only sons provide for parents.
Daughters move in with their
husbands after marriage and enjoy life.
Move!
You and your pearls of wisdom!
-Move aside!
-Do you get it, you witch?
Oh, my God!
This is what happens if you open
your mouth unnecessarily.
-Get your hands off me!
-I shouldn't have helped him!
Isn't this a reserved compartment?
What's that stench?
Dried fish? Yuck!
Well, you won't stop eating
once you taste this.
We will get off at Tsundur.
These seats will be all yours.
This is express train.
It doesn't stop at Tsundur.
It does! For the last six months,
our boy has not let
a single train pass Tsundur
without stopping there.
-That is Maha.
-Without so much as causing a ruckus!
So every time I travel to Vijayawada,
I've to deal with this crap?
You can keep these precious seats
all for yourself.
We won't be traveling
in trains anymore.
Then how are you going to travel?
-We're going to fly!
-Fly?
-He's bringing a plane to us!
-Yes!
-Who?
-Our Maha!
On this strange land
Brought to life by God
Behold the games of man
Behold the games
Behold man's mad games
On this round ball of dirt
Behold the strange game of man
When his eyelids last shut
He is but a procession on a hearse
Savor these sips of toddy
The one who's bathed
In toddy above is watching you
Rich or poor
All are dealt the same notch
In their final passage
all get blown the conch
Rich or poor,
all are dealt the same notch
On their final passage,
all get blown the conch
Evolved from apes we may have,
but our race saw no evolution
Behold our fate
Behold our ethics
Experience being a monkey
Its race and its ethics
Else, let it go and dance
Before the end of sweetness between us
This music can even raise the dead
The wraps come undone
when the drunks dance with joy
The wails of women light up and soar
Legions of near and dear
yet no one to tag along with him
Acres of lands were his
yet six feet of soil is what is
Legions of near and dear
yet no one to tag along with him
Acres of lands were his
yet six feet of soil is what is
The one dancing in the black shirt
is the groom.
-What!
-What is he doing?
The bride's family is here.
What are you doing?
-Did we come for this?
-This is humiliating.
They're staring at you.
Who cares?
That man danced for every death here.
The whole village
should dance on his death.
-Come and dance!
-Alright. Let's rock it!
-God forbid she starts dancing!
-Stop it.
Let's go.
Rocks. Palm trees.
Barren lands.
It'll all be your daughter's.
Yeah right! The groom doesn't seem
interested in the marriage.
Oh, no. He's keen too.
-Come on. Let's go inside.
-Come on!
Please have some fryums.
Did we come all the way
to eat fryums?
Don't you have cakes?
There's no toilet
how can they offer cakes?
Don't shush me.
It's the truth.
Since we're talking truths,
I'm completely broke.
I've a huge loan
and all I earn goes for repayment.
-Hey.
-No, he is just joking.
This land's worth a lot of money.
All I have is an idea
to start an airline.
But 24 banks have rejected it.
Look, mister.
Men are in a queue to marry
my beautiful and talented daughter.
I've been rejected by 20 men
so far.
-Shh! Silly girl. Shut up.
-Why?
I don't sew, cook, dance, or sing.
Mr. Military! She's just pulling your leg.
-She knows all that and more, right?
-Ignore him.
But I won't do any of it.
I just want to start a bakery.
Now that they have blurted out the truth,
there's nothing to talk about.
-Let's eat.
-Okay. Let's go.
-Let's eat and call it a day.
-Wait a minute.
It's not our tradition to eat unless
the discussion is fruitful.
And we don't let our guests go hungry.
-Let's go and eat!
-What?
So your friend's bringing planes
to this village?
-Yeah, bro.
-Enough.
Have you been on an airplane?
"Been on one"?
What are you talking?
I have a close friend who's a pilot.
He lets me drive when he gets tired.
It is true, believe me.
How will you finance your airline?
Hey, that's grown-up talk.
Why are you asking about it?
That's why I'm asking.
Let her ask.
So, 20 men rejected you?
Twenty four banks rejected you, right?
Can we talk about that?
They weren't that bright.
Those men weren't either.
One, two, three.
Just three steps to start an airline!
Seems easy.
Starting a bakery is easier.
Why haven't you done that yet?
I'm stuck at step one.
Looking for finance.
I'm waiting for money.
I know banks.
What is 'ven-tu-r capitalist'?
Venture Capitalist.
Banks give loans against collateral.
But for Venture Capitalist, VC
your idea is your collateral.
You get funds if they like your idea.
Oh!
Then you must find a VC.
Who is that? A VC?
-Did you like food?
-Yes, it is good.
Paresh Goswami.
He owns Jaz Airlines.
He realized his dream
with little to no help.
My hero.
With so many basic needs unfulfilled
in our country
who needs planes?
Stop talking like that.
A century ago,
they said we don't need electricity.
Fifty years ago,
they said we don't need cars.
-Who decides that?
-That is right.
The rich decide for the rest.
-Forget it. You won't get it.
-Is it? Shut up and eat.
Okay.
Okay with what?
With marrying you.
That was quick.
Are you insane?
Sometimes, no matter how hard we think,
we end up doing what we want.
-I don't like to waste time.
-That's Maha!
But I give enough thought
before making up my mind.
-There she goes.
- You'll know my decision in the morning.
That's my girl! Eat, dear.
You fussed about eating here.
But you missed the train
and has to stay back.
That is fate.
That way.
Hey!
You have a big house in the village.
Why do you stay in a place
where there's no electricity?
Getting electricity is no big deal.
Even teacher Rajaram's house
didn't have electricity 20 years ago.
With determination anything is possible.
-Hey! Air India!
-Air India! Air India!
-Air India!
-Where are you going?
I'm going to board Air India, Dad.
You want planes
when there are no roads?
First, learn to cut hair!
Is it a law that a son must do
his father's trade?
No matter what they study,
it's their fate
to get into the family business?
Keep the pot on your head, kid.
I'll do the rest in the morning.
Dad, it would look awkward!
What if I cut off your ear
in the dark?
First make the train
stop at our village.
Tsundur folks must go till Tenali
to take a train.
My father, the six-fingered
school teacher,
wrote numerous letters to the government
to make the train stop here.
How long will you keep writing?
As long as I can hold a pen.
Politicians go around happily
in trains and planes!
Why would they care about us?
The teacher kept writing petitions,
but nothing changed.
I picked up a stone.
-Hear us, Central Government!
-Stop the express train here!
-Tsundur beseeches you!
-Deceive us, no more!
Down with police brutality!
We want the train to stop here.
Stop it, stop it.
Stop the train here!
We want the train!
Stop it, stop it.
Maha!
Kasi!
-Kasi?
-Maha.
Take this.
-I can't open my eye.
-You'll be fine! I'm here!
What happened?
Oh my god! You're bleeding!
Your son pelted stones
to stop the train at Tsundur.
Kasi's badly injured.
He could have lost an eye.
What? Is it true?
Come on in first.
He would've been arrested!
They let him go because he's my son!
But God, the way they looked at me.
I was so ashamed!
The people of the village
honor my words,
but my own son
doesn't listen to me.
Dad, you've always said
time's precious.
And that the train stopping here
will change our lives.
You talk a lot about change.
Shouldn't I make it happen?
Hey, don't act like a stupid person.
Aren't you educated?
You're a teacher's son!
Stupid fellow.
If you want the train to stop here,
you should write to the division head.
Do you get it?
Can you do that?
You wrote petitions.
-Maha? Maha?
-What happened?
We got electricity because of that.
Get inside!
Not that petition, mom!
I know which petition
he's talking about.
Let him talk.
He hasn't eaten!
You know he blabbers
when he's hungry!
-Come in.
-If he has the guts, let him say it!
First thing tomorrow,
I'll have him arrested.
Don't say that.
He's our son!
What did you do when mom had
pregnancy complications?
You just sent petitions
asking for a medical camp!
-You'll have me arrested?
-Hey.
You should be arrested
for killing your child!
-Maha! Don't talk about it.
-Quiet, Mom!
Even now we took Kasi to town.
This armchair idealist will bury us all
with his petitions!
You're a bloody failure!
And will always be one!
Oh, my God!
What have you done? Maha...
If violence is wrong,
then why the hell did you just hit me?
Maha, mind your language.
-Thanks for the lesson, son.
-Oh, God.
Don't even light my pyre
when I die.
-Listen to me.
-Leave!
Maha!
What have you done?
Son, where are you going?
He's leaving!
Hey, Maha, don't go.
Where are you going?
And then what happened?
Then I joined the National Defense Academy
and then the Air Force.
Quite the angry man!
Were you as bad in the Air Force?
He says the snacks don't reach him.
-All the postal guys...
-Aunt!
Show it to him.
-The postal guys eat them up.
-Maha has sent a letter.
I'm sending two boxes this time!
With a note saying...
"You can take one box,
but give the other to my son."
Get it here!
Should I read it out?
I am a third grader,
and a teacher's wife!
I can read myself.
Look at him writing chits.
Writes letters for his son
and then hides them!
I will shred them one day!
"Dear Mom."
Look! He's listening.
"And dear Kasi...
Hope all is well.
I'm good here."
This shows how much he loves us.
"I passed my ex-cams, Mom."
-It's an 'exam', Aunt!
-That's what I said. Shut up!
"Chaitanya stood first.
And I was second.
Seby stood fourth.
I am a pilot officer
Chandra Mahesh Kanayanam now.
There's an Officer called Naidu
who torments me with his rules
and tortures me with do's and don'ts,
just like our teacher!"
Bring this stupid Naidu to me.
I'm going to break his neck
like I do with chickens.
Move round and round
Like a surging hurricane
Stomp over arrogance
Like a bull off its leash
A streak like the lightning
Tear it all down
Punch it and spread it dry
Then, dust it off and toss it out
Sir!
Come on, trainees!
Double up!
Move fast, I say!
Kasi, I'm fine! How are you?
Where's mom?
She's fine!
Get her quick!
I only have three minutes!
She's bringing your father!
She'll be here any second!
Hang on!
She's here, Maha!
Aunty, hurry up!
Ask them to hurry!
His leg hurts.
-Here, Aunt!
-Give it to me.
Hello, Maha?
-Mom?
-Maha? Your dad's come.
-Mom?-Shall I put him on, Maha.
-Mom, I can hear you.
-Maha?
I can't hear anything.
I can hear you.
Please talk.
Buddy?
Hello?
-Ask her to talk.-Can you hear me?
-Hello!
-Give it to his dad!
-The line got disconnected!
-Oh, no.
Kasi, I can hear you.
Give the receiver to dad.
Why will he talk to a failure?
He won't talk to me.
What are you saying?
Hold him!
Hello. Mom!
I'll just make one more call!
-Uncle?
-Please wait, dear.
-Chandra Mahesh?
-Sir!
People are waiting.
Everyone gets only three minutes.
Call next month!
Move! Move!
Logistically we can save a lot, sir.
How will one MI-26 alone suffice?
Since it's a joint exercise
with army,
we can transport airmen
in their armored troop carriers.
One chopper will do.
We ration fuel
and cut extra costs.
You will cut down nothing, Chandra Mahesh.
Don't be stingy.
Intelligence says,
the insurgent activity has risen
near the Sinhagad Fort.
We eliminate risk by increasing
our ground numbers.
And then we can go ahead, sir.
It's not being stingy,
It's being smart, sir.
-So... Chaitanya?
-Sir!
Is he saying I'm dumb?
No, sir!
Fifty rounds around the parade ground!
Fifty kilos dead weight!
Take your friends with you!
Hundred rounds. Eighty kilos.
In one and a half hours.
Move!
Baby, Baby? Hey, Baby?
-Hey, get up!
-Hey.
What are you doing with him
so late at night?
Get up!
Like a churn
You shook up my heart
Like in a war
You have shaken up my life
Like a pearl born in a shell
deep down in the ocean of milk
Give me a few glimpses of your beauty
to make me desire for more
You tigress!
Oh, tigress
This boy is your bounty
-Hey, Kasi!
-Yes, buddy?
Why is she so mad?
You two were just talking, right?
Why should I tell you?
After so many rejections,
I was scared,
my niece will remain a spinster.
This is an auspicious month.
Got to book a marriage hall soon!
You brought it this far.
Excellent job!
Over there.
He looks dashing, doesn't he?
No.
What the hell?
Are you saying no
to the marriage in the hall?
I am saying no to the marriage.
The boy himself has agreed!
Why are you declining?
Did you ask those 20 men
why they rejected me?
-That's different!
-Shut up.
May I ask why?
Yes! Yes you may!
You're already married
to airplane!
I'm married, too.
Let's make something
out of that first.
Serves you right for your arrogance.
The devil's just like you!
No loss, buddy.
She looks like a bun, anyway.
We can find someone better than her.
Shut up.
I'm sure she has her reasons.
Unbelievable.
Hey broker,
I'll deal with you later.
Did you bring us all the way to say no?
-What's your problem?
-What is your problem!
That I rejected him?
Or that you couldn't reject
your husband?
He is a good guy.
You can't find anyone like him.
-Drop them off.
-No way, buddy!
Let them walk.
It's a waste of fuel.
Hey, get into the vehicle.
Wealth and festivities, you lured away
I lay awake at nights
for you hacked away at my sleep
My wings are caught in the storm
You stirred my heart like a tornado
Slipping spectacles onto my heart
you have shown me your tricks
By breaking the reins of my youth
You have sung your song
You shook me up
BABY BAKERY
I like you, lady
Slipping spectacles onto my heart
You have shown me your tricks
By breaking the reins of my youth
You have sung your song
-We cannot give loans for airplanes.
-Sir, please listen to me.
You know we are a tiny rural bank.
Morning, ma'am.
Can I meet Mr. Mittal, Venture Capitalist?
- I am Chandra--
-I have many of these already, sir.
-I'll send it to the aviation minister.
-Thank you, sir.
A simple thing to say
spoken brash and blunt
I am amused to see myself in you
whenever you come in my sight
I wonder if I will ever lay my eyes
on a girl like you
Even if I am delayed by millennia
I will still seek you out
O my dimple-cheeked bird
I have wed you
And now, I am born again
Slipping spectacles onto my heart
You have shown me your tricks
By breaking the reins of my youth
You have sung your song
I can't meet anyone right now.
I'm late for my flight.
Sir.
-Mam, one meeting--
-Please give your card over there.
You always make these fritters.
Why can't you make cakes?
Look at the mugs wanting cakes!
Baby's Cakes!
Sweets from Tenali
for the spicy tongues of Guntur!
-Mr. Paresh Goswami...
-Look!
I already have a hundred of your cards!
You can't meet him.
Why don't you understand?
Are you a fortune teller
or a programmer?
-The logic's wrong. Override it.
-One second.
It's running, sir!
Source code ready!
Brilliant, sir!
It is running, sir!
Superb, sir!
Oh, really?
How many millions
are you going to make from this?
Corrupting IIT kids
with his lofty ideas!
You should become a professor at IIT, sir.
-Yes, sir. You should become a professor.
-Yes, sir.
Yes, sir!
You should!
If I was that smart,
I would have moved out of his place.
Both of you quit the Air Force
yapping about some big dreams.
What did you achieve...
Son-in-law!
Sebastian!
You need an ex-serviceman loan, right?
-Your friend's reputation precedes him.
-Bring my bag.
Especially now with Naidu sitting
in Tambaram!
-He's not going to sign.
-I can't hear you!
You eat my food
and pretend to not hear me.
-I can't hear you.
-Of course, you don't.
Thank you.
This loan won't be approved
without Naidu's recommendation letter.
So, I want you to shut up, okay?
Che went through a lot
trouble to get this appointment.
-So, you shut up! Understand?
-Hmm.
What "Hmm"?
Are you listening to me.
-I'm not deaf!
-Good boy! Go, go.
Chandra Mahesh,
let me spell it out for you.
Even though I can,
I won't sign this recommendation letter.
You want my best pilot Chaitanya to resign
and ruin his life.
I don't like people who break rules.
-You're not fit to be a leader!
-Let's go.
Sir.
Hey, Seby and Maha.
What happened?
The same crap even after all these years.
-Egoistic jackasses, both!
-Maha, stop.
Forget him and the banks.
Let's figure out our next move.
I just did.
Hold on, Maha.
-Twenty thousand rupees, yes?
-Yes.
-Have a nice journey.
-Thank you.
These people have nothing better to do.
Sir, I've just two boxes
of fryum and pickles.
-They'll be ruined if I check them in!
-That is not my problem, ma'am.
-You're delaying the passengers.
-My sister's pregnant.
Please come forward, sir.
-Do you know about pregnancy cravings?
-You have to check it in.
You are a man.
How can you know about it?
Ma'am, I can't help you.
Have you ever been pregnant?
Please send the manager
to counter number four.
Good. Call the manager!
-Is she a lady, she'll understand.
-Excuse me, ma'am.
I'll take them. No problem.
-I can take them.
-Thank you very much, sir.
Look, he is with me.
Check me in now!
-Check me in, I say!
-Sure, ma'am.
Yes, give it to me.
You won't run off with these, will you?
Fryums and pickles.
Are you a reporter?
Yes, how did you know?
You ask too many questions.
Yeah!
Actually, this flight is full of media.
Paresh Goswami himself is flying us
to the RRTV Awards.
-Is that where you are going?
-Yes.
I've not seen you
in media before.
I'm Chitra Ramarao.
Senior Producer, All India Radio.
Okay.
Where are you going?
Am I bothering you
with my questions?
I still want an answer.
Please tell me.
-Where are you going?
-Thanks.
-To meet someone.
-Whom?
Good afternoon, sir.
-Excuse me.
-Sir?
My brother Bhawarlal's outside.
-Please send him in.
-Sure, sir! Sure, sir!
-Shall I cancel the flight?
-No, no.
It's just an anxiety attack.
It's okay.
Change your shirt.
Take your pill.
Bhawar.
Do the staff use the same restrooms
as the guests?
A steward just used one.
I'll have it cleaned.
Shivdas Airport Services.
I'll have him fired.
The Paresh Goswami?
Why do you want to meet such a big shot?
To discuss a business partnership.
There's no way you can meet him.
I'll make him my business partner.
Are you kidding?
He won't even talk to you.
Want to bet?
-What if he did?
-Out of the question.
At most, we can just applaud his speech.
Why are you getting up?
That call's for business class.
You didn't say what you'll do
if you lose.
I'll tell you what to do
when I win.
Business class?
You must be really rich.
Then why wait in the queue?
You're strange!
You spent 40,000
to fly in business class?
Didn't you say
I can't meet him at the event?
Hence, business class.
You don't need 40,000,
twenty's enough.
I'll be returning by train.
I'm not rich, I emptied
my bank account to buy the ticket.
Sir, anyways, please take care
of my fryums and pickles.
-Be careful.
-Yeah.
Good evening, sir.
Welcome on board.
Ladies and gentlemen, this is
Captain Sharma from the flight deck.
On behalf of first officer Matthew
and the crew,
we welcome you all
onboard Jaz Airlines, JZ 433
Chennai to Mumbai.
We have with us today,
our chairman, Mr. Goswami...
- Mr. Paresh, hello.-Our heartiest welcome to you, sir.
Right, sir.
I'll see you in Bombay.
Congratulations on the award, sir.
Proud moment for the Jaz family.
Hello, sir.
I'm Chandra Mahesh.
You're the inspiration
for my airline.
May I request you
to return to your seat, sir?
-Right, sir.
-It's fine.
Pleasure, sir.
You intend to start an airline?
Yes, sir.
An airline for the common man.
To travel at low-cost.
-Chandrababu?
-It's Chandra Mahesh.
Would these people you speak of
want three square meals a day
or fly in a plane?
Sir, I won't confuse them
with the choices.
With my ticket fare,
they can do both.
Are you planning
some kind of social service?
I want to execute this idea
with you, sir.
Everyone in here has an idea
to become a billionaire.
They all sound great.
But practically impossible.
I never waste time
talking about the impossible.
My idea's practically possible.
So you want to sell tickets
at a cheap price and still be profitable.
You're saying this didn't occur to us?
Yes, sir.
Today, no Indian can book air tickets
without a travel agency.
We all know that.
A big chunk of the fare goes
to the travel agent.
Like it goes to the middlemen
in farming.
What if we bypass that?
Bypass a travel agency?
Then how will customers book tickets?
The internet!
They book tickets
through computers.
Wow!
So a farmer who's never seen a computer
nor the internet
will book tickets thus and fly.
Fantastic!
Internet's available in 500 post offices
in AP alone.
And 1,453 Reliance petrol bunks
all over India has an internet facility.
They can book there!
Then the farmers won't need computers,
right?
But this requires
specialized booking software.
I don't think you're aware of it.
You must be aware of Interworld.
They make ticketing software
for all major airlines.
They've agreed to do it for me.
You can make
a tailor fly alongside a textile baron.
-Yes, I can make that happen.
-Sir.
But I won't.
Why, sir?
Would anyone want to see
beggars and coolies on planes?
I don't want my passengers to suffer.
Is that why
your airfare is so expensive?
I have an airline to run, my friend.
-What you're doing is...
-Get him out.
Put him in economy.
Why the fuck should I go?
I've bought the ticket.
Lay a hand on me,
I'll rip your throat out.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is Captain Sharma again,
from the flight deck.
Unfortunately, the aircraft is developed
a technical snag.
We need to turn around to Chennai.
You own the ticket.
I own the plane, my friend.
-This way. sir.
-This way.
I know the drill.
My job here's done.
Ma'am.
Your fryums and pickles.
-Thank you.
-See you.
-Chandra Mahesh, careful.
-Yeah? Thanks.
Bye.
Mr. Chandra Mahesh,
I was on that flight, too.
I heard what you told Paresh.
I'm Prakash Babu.
SCI Venture Capitalists.
I know.
I've been to your office many times.
Alright.
I'll give you the time now.
Okay?
Five minutes.
Come along.
-Take care of table two.
-Okay, sir.
Mahesh, if you're hungry,
we could've gone
to the five-star hotel nearby.
There's no better place
to explain my idea to you, sir.
-Brother, how are you?
-Fine, brother.
-What can I get you? Okay.
-Dosa, please.
What's the connection
between Udupi hotel and airline?
Today, an air ticket to Delhi
costs Rs. 12,000.
First class costs 20,000.
Definitely.
Running airline is an expensive affair.
Flight maintenance, hangar charges,
pilot salary, fuel costs...
It's a costly business!
Dig in.
Please have it.
They did not get Poori. Please check.
How is it, sir?
Actually, it's tasty.
-Very good.
-Thank you, sir!
It's delicious.
Brother!
-Where do you get your provisions?
-Chintamani stores at More market!
Who is their biggest customer?
The five-star hotel
in the neighboring street.
You know what's funny?
We provide dinner for their staff too!
You continue, please.
Have you had dosa
at the five-star hotel nearby?
When I get good dosa here
for 16 bucks,
why will I waste 200 bucks there?
Sure, brother.
-The dosa's great here. Enjoy!
-Okay, brother.
Do you get it, sir?
Everyone's happy.
The same dish is sold under a fancy name
at the five-star hotel.
Only difference is, this is cheaper.
But no difference
in taste and hygiene.
No needless expenses.
My airline will operate in the same way.
Why have food and newspapers
on an hour-long flight?
I will neither provide them
nor charge for them.
Ten percent of costs drop right away.
We keep our flights very light.
No extra food no staff.
Other airlines do two trips a day.
We will do six.
Six trips?
How?
There is Flight Duty Time Limitation.
Staff cannot fly
for more than eight hours.
Let's plan three shifts.
Three shifts.
Eighteen hours of flying time.
Deduct C&D checks, cleaning, and fueling,
we still fly 14 hours.
Only humans tire.
Planes don't, right?
But, this isn't the norm.
It's not the convention.
Let's change it.
Let's break every damn rule.
Look, sir.
No table's empty,
no waiter's idle.
Simply put,
our airline's the Udupi Hotel in the sky.
You didn't tell me you were starting
an Udupi Hotel!
-Not on this street.
-Then, it's fine!
-If I...
-Say no?
I've tried 23 VCs and 56 banks
so far.
And all they said was,
"Who is this crazy fool?"
If you say the same,
I'll just go find VC number 24.
I'm done.
-Excuse me.
-Sure.
-Mahesh.
-Sir!
Come to my office next month.
8th of April.
Convince the rest of the board.
-Okay? Bye.
-Yeah.
There's a girl named Nagalakshmi.
My mom's blackmailing me
into meeting her.
Let me go over there
and set that right!
The kids have gone nuts after you
showed them that film on planes.
We were doomed to carts, Subba.
At least, let the kids fly!
My bike can't go any faster!
Maha, wait!
WELCOME TO
GUNTUR MUNICIPAL ASSOCIATION
Unfortunately, I borrowed
from that damn loan shark Ravi!
He comes here every day without fail
and hounds me for money!
Hey, you bloody...
Isn't this that girl's shop?
Your mom told us to meet Nagalakshmi.
Let's go!
-Let's buy sweets!
-Hello, son-in-law!
What brings you here?
Get down.
You rejected us
and now call him son-in-law?
Load up two kilos of cakes!
Is this a scrap shop? It's a bakery!
It's "pack two kilos of cakes."
Whatever!
Give me samples of these two.
Eating for free is called 'sampling', eh?
Nasty habit!
How dare you come here
after calling me a bun?
Let's go, buddy.
It's a bullshit bakery!
Are you married?
Yes. Two kids. You?
-What about you?
-We're meeting a prospective bride.
That's why we stopped here
for sweets.
So you've been at it for three years?
Where's the airplane company?
You know VC?
The venture capitalist?
They've okayed my project.
Few formalities left on DGCA licenses,
and NOC.
So you're still on the step one?
I'm already on the step three!
Hello?
I'm going to launch in a month!
-I see...
-Ah, now you're gobsmacked?
You wish!
Had you bought an auto or bus,
you would've made some money!
What does your husband
do for a living?
We're set to open another branch,
mind you!
What does the little one want?
-Freshly made cakes!
-Why are you crying?
-Fifty rupees discount for you!
-Do you want a cake?
Okay, don't cry!
Why is he so pissed?
-Shall we go?
-Let's eat a cake.
Do you call this cake?
It's disgusting.
Sugary crap!
Spit it out!
It's pretty good, buddy!
Hey.
No human can eat these.
Damn country bumpkins!
Country brute.
Would any sane person open a bakery
near a liquor shop?
Should've been near a school
or college.
You need brains to work that out!
Buddy!
Maha!
I found out something.
Nothing happened.
What are you talking about?
That bun girl isn't married yet!
Her loudmouth uncle told me!
Can I eat her cakes now?
Sweets from Tenali
for the spicy tongues of Guntur!
Milk cakes! Cheesecakes!
Butter cakes!
Buy one, get one free!
Baby's cakes!
Yummy cakes!
-Those were your friend's kids, right?
-Amazing taste.
Why did you bluff?
Paneer cake!
Made by Baby Bakery!
-Why did you lie to me?
-Milk cake, butter cake,
-Hey, bun face!
-Baby...
Listen to me!
The world calls us crackpots.
No one would come forward
to marry us.
So why don't we get married?
What do you say?
Oh, really?
So why didn't you see this crackpot
in three years?
Back then,
I couldn't even feed myself.
Those barren lands are green now!
Good income!
My business kicks off in a month!
Good enough, right?
Amazing taste! Super taste!
Baby's Bakery!
And if it fails?
Who says it's only a husband
who provides for the wife?
Won't you feed me?
What do you say, bun face?
I got three conditions.
What are they?
It's a bait, kiddo.
Don't fall for it!
One, it's our money,
not your money or my money.
Got it.
Two, my business
is as important as yours. Got it?
Sure.
This is 2.1, your brain can't process
more than two points.
-Hey.
-Our family's very important to me.
And if you let us down,
I'll poison your food!
If you agree to these conditions,
we can marry tomorrow.
I already said yes to all of it!
You better think hard
because I won't divorce you.
I won't ask for it either.
Okay. How come you agreed now?
Sometimes,
no matter how hard we think,
we end up doing what we want.
Why waste time?
Come on over!
Buy one loony,
get another free!
Buy two loonies,
get both free!
Both loonies are available!
Come get them!
Kohl-eyes light up looking at you
Oh boy
Words fail me
As if I am chewing on the water
Like a home adorned with colorful
Designs my heart is resounding with joy
Like gathered neem leaves
A procession is arriving my way
You caress me like the coins
In the folds of my saree
You are the noise
That keeps me up all night
My desires, once like a dried-up forest
Suddenly blossom
My heart revolves around you
And asks to give me yours
I, Sundari aka Baby,
Who lives in Tenali...
To all of you who came to this wedding
jam cakes will be provided.
With cameraman Rani, this is Mangaraju.
Ward off the evil eye!
Just thirty bucks?
-You deserve less.
-Oh, really?
Like the pigeon perched atop a tower
I look for you in directions many
Whenever I hear a little flutter
My heart hops like a hare
Should I open my heart and spill
Or shed my shame and tell?
I desire no one but you
You pinch my cheek
And tame the wild fire I hold tight
Sting me like a wasp
Coil around me like a python
Baby, for your new bakery.
-Baby?
-Yes, bro?
-Can I hang it here?
-Put it over there!
When you see it,
you'll be stunned, madam.
With the college nearby,
the business will soar.
Imagine my cakes being sold here.
Do you know what this is?
A pager.
We can talk easily
if it is a phone, right?
-What to do with it?
-It's for you.
This thing looks a little off!
You try drawing it!
As the plane's weight increases,
so will fuel cost.
An airline in America...
Pay attention!
They cut down 500 pounds
by not painting their flights!
That's four people flying for free!
So you don't like weight?
Without a sword
You nipped my beauty
Without the touch of your fingernail
You pinched my waist!
Oh my
You behave like you are unaware
You ignite and slide away
So cleverly
When I am next to you
Like a pot of spicy fish curry
My youth simmers
Like a hot plate of delicacy
I'll caress your taste buds
Do savor it all day
Crack the knuckles of my fingers slowly
Smoothen out the folds of my saree
The craze for you has trapped me
And it refuses to leave
I'll string you onto me
Like a chain of black beads
I'll attach you to me
Like backbone
To sum it up, passengers must be able to
buy plane tickets, like they do soaps.
Together, we can make this happen.
That's it.
Thank you.
Indian Airlines
has a thousand crore debt.
And you want to make profits
with thousand rupee tickets to Delhi?
My competitor is the Indian Railways,
not Indian Airlines.
-Indian Railways?
-And they are doing very well.
A Boeing plane costs 136 crores,
Mr. Mahesh.
Even a second-hand one
costs 90 crores.
What can you do with just ten crores?
I didn't say I was buying planes.
We'll lease them.
What if your revenue is less
than expected?
At 70% occupancy, like most airlines,
we can earn 12.42 crores.
That's a profit of 4.14 crores.
Sounds impossible.
-Deeksha?
-He's right.
Oh! Let me see that!
If it's less than 70% occupancy?
If it's 70% at ten thousand rupees
per ticket,
won't I get at least 50% occupancy
with thousand rupee tickets?
You are talking way below market rates.
Who will lease Boeings to you
at such low rates?
-PlaneAm.
-Really?
The Twin Tower attack
affected their airline business.
They're willing to give us planes
at half the price.
Congratulations, Mahesh.
They've sanctioned funds.
If we get the DGCA license
then we can launch our airline.
Well done, Maha.
All thanks to you, sir.
-No, no. It's okay.
-If you weren't here...
-Just one thing.
-Sir.
Can you get an advance ready
and reserve the planes right away?
Advance?
-You want me to pay the advance?
-Yes.
-How much would you need, Mahesh?
-47 lakhs.
It will take at least four to five months
to release funds.
If PlaneAm hikes their rates
in the meantime,
or if someone else steals this idea,
we'll be in trouble.
Our entire business hinges on this.
Unlicensed planes can't fly into India.
Get them to Malaysia
and start painting and stickering there.
We'll get them to India
once we get the license.
I like this idea, sir.
I'll handle this.
Folks come by to get loans
for tractors and autos.
You're the first to ask for airplanes!
Alright then.
What a proud moment
if one of ours starts an airline!
I had a lot of dreams in my youth.
But no one gave me money then.
Projected profit
for the first six months...
That's okay.
I'm allergic to computers.
-How much, ma'am? 47 lakhs?
-Yes. 47 lakhs.
Check if this loan's feasible.
Don't mistake me.
Just standard procedure.
Depending on current rates,
its value is 40 lakhs.
They want an excess of seven lakhs!
We can't give money
without these documents.
He's my teacher's son!
-Give him the money.
-Alright.
Sign these documents, ma'am.
You're starting a business.
It is good to face east and sign.
If you default payment by even a day
the next three months,
-you'll have to pay two-fold interest.
-I'll pay on time.
Brother, that's okay.
Ma'am, please go.
I'll send the money over.
-What's next?
-Get a license from the DGCA.
-What's that?
-Like the RTO office in town?
We need a license from them to fly.
Replay the reel from the beginning!
Okay, sir.
I will take care of this.
Why did you give him an appointment?
He was referred by Prakash Babu
from SCI.
He's been waiting for two months.
He should know
meeting DGCA isn't easy.
-Let him wait.
-Yes, sir.
Sir, you asked me to come to 8:30 am,
but I was here at 7 am.
I was here before the peon.
Yet, you haven't called me.
-Please wait!
-Sir...
-Sir, first appointment was given to me.
-Excuse me.
Get going, all of you.
Sir will be back in an hour.
Car's ready, sir.
I'm Mahesh.
Mr. Prakash Babu reference.
-I'm sorry. You're still here?
-It's alright.
I have an urgent meeting
with the new aviation minister.
-Can we meet tomorrow?
-Sure, sir.
-Nice.
-Thank you.
Bye.
-Good morning, sir.
-Good morning.
Oh, Mahesh.
-I went through your documents.
-Oh, thanks.
-Very interesting.
-Sir.
We can wrap it up tomorrow, right?
-Yes.
-No problem, right?
-Okay, sir. I'll wait.
-Nice.
Did you set up a meeting
with the aviation minister?
I spoke to his PA.
-When is it?
-Tomorrow.
Mahesh?
Sir?
We wrap it up today, right?
He's off for a week.
Didn't you know?
Come back later.
You're his assistant, right?
It's your job to keep him posted.
You're a smart guy, right?
I can only tell you what he tells me to.
How long will you make me wait!
Just for one meeting...
I don't have the time or money for this.
-Please, sir.
-Then why do you keep coming, sir?
Do you know Ratan Tata, Mahesh?
He waited here for 20 years
to start Tata Airlines.
He failed.
And you are a nobody, Mahesh.
Get going.
Understand, man.
Don't show up next week!
Either pay the interest
or give your house to Ravi.
Don't you trust us?
We will return your money.
Painting charges ate up all our money!
Just two lakhs left!
A scientist's amazing journey
from Rameswaram to the Rashtrapati Bhavan.
A special interview
with President Abdul Kalam
by Chitra Ramarao,
our senior news reporter from Chennai.
This is All India Radio.
An amazing journey
from Rameswaram to the Rashtrapati Bhavan.
Damn!
So much security!
-If we get caught, we're doomed!
-We won't.
That stupid bet was a joke!
This isn't like meeting Paresh
on a jet!
We can't just sneak in
through the door!
Can I tell you something?
I learned it from my experience.
If the door's ajar,
don't just get a foot in. Dash in!
I can't lie to the President, Mahesh.
Hello!
It's not wrong to lie
for a good cause.
-Falsehood takes on truth's nature.
-What?
It is said so in the Bhagavad Gita!
The man inside knows it well! Madam.
It's not news
if I don't meet him.
-But...
-Sir, this way.
-Okay.
-Yes, sir.
If I do meet him,
you get an exclusive headline!
Do you really think I'm convinced?
I'm staking everything to do this
only because I'm just another sheep
among a billion here!
And I hope you won't become one.
-You better deliver...
-Excuse me, ma'am.
- ...on your promises.
-Please follow me.
Ma'am, papers, please.
One second.
-This is for...
-Thank You.
Mr. Raghunandan.
My voice recordist.
Just a pen.
By the way, don't quote anything inside.
You were doing it all wrong!
I'm Chitra Ramarao.
This is my voice recordist, Raghunandan.
Raghunandan, Raghunandan.
I'm Chitra Ramarao.
This is my voice recordist, Raghunandan.
This way, please.
Your ID?
-Sir, your ID, please.
-Yeah.
See, actually, we both are a team.
This is my ID.
Sir, I need to see your ID.
Raghunandan, voice recordist.
Sir, your photo ID, please.
See, we have documentation
from downstairs.
-No, ma'am!
-Sir, I'm not from the radio station.
I'm Chandra Mahesh Kanayanam.
I just need two minutes.
-Please let me see him, sir. Please, sir.
-No, you are not allowed.
Please listen to me.
Sir.
If I could make
a two days trip in two hours,
I would've seen my father alive!
I want to start a low cost airline,
but they won't let me, sir!
-Sir!
-Mister?
Are you a Telugu?
Yes, sir!
I just need two minutes of your time!
After that, if you think I'm wrong,
have me arrested!
-Dhanraj, please let him in.
-Yes, sir!
Security under control.
-Good day, sir.
-Greetings, sir.
Greetings!
I'm from a small village
near Tsundur.
My father was a government school teacher.
Hello?
-Maha.-Mom?
Mom?
Your father's been bedridden
for two weeks now.
He's holding on just to see you.
The doctor says he won't survive.
Tell dad I'll be home tomorrow by 11 AM.
My son, Maha!
-I'll be there! Be brave!
-Hurry!
-I'll come, Mom!
-Come soon!
Oh, God.
-Be careful.
-For the flight fare!
Hurry!
You can catch the 8 pm flight!
-I'll do the money order.
-Shut up!
This is 6,000.
The ticket is for 11,200 business-class.
Economy costs 6,000, right?
Those are fully booked now, sir.
Excuse me, sir. Please.
No...
Is there anything else you can do?
-I'm sorry. We don't give discounts.
-Any cancellation?
Sir, here you go with your money.
Please move.
-I need...
-Sir, try and understand.
Please move aside.
Ma'am, please.
-Excuse me.
-Sir.
My dad's unwell.
I need to meet him.
I only have 6,000, but she is asking me
to take a first-class...
Please move. They're waiting.
Alright! I'll get the money.
How much time do I have?
-My God!
-How much time do I have?
Five minutes.
Excuse me.
Move, now.
When is the next flight?
When is it?
In two days.
Oh, God! The smell.
Please move aside, sir!
Two days!
Two...
Sir. Sir. Sir.
My father's unwell, sir.
I need to buy a ticket.
It's urgent.
It's an emergency, sir.
When you're flying,
you should bring money.
Okay?
Ma'am.
Ma'am, If you can
please help me.
Sir, I need to get this ticket.
-Can you help me with some more money?
-Sorry mister, no.
Is he mad?
Crazy people.
Ma'am.
Time is running out.
My father is not well.
It's an emergency.
-Boarding closes in five minutes.
-No, just leave.
I need to go to Hyderabad.
The last plane leaves in five minutes.
Sir.
It's an emergency.
My father is very sick.
I need to see him.
I don't have money for a ticket.
-Please give him some, dad.
-Sir, at 11 o'clock...
Gautam, just shut up
and read your comic.
Please lend me the money!
I can give you...
I can give you my gold ring!
I can give you my address
and phone number.
Sir, please.
Please understand!
Security!
What's with this nuisance?
Sir, please help me.
Sir, I can...
I can show you my...
I'm an '87 batch Air Force Officer.
Please can somebody understand?
Can somebody please help me?
Give me your address and phone number,
I can definitely give the money back.
I promise. I promise.
I really need this money.
Boarding closes in five minutes!
I'm Chandra Mahesh.
House number 7,
Anjaneyaswami temple street,
Kullupalam,
Tsundur, Guntur district-522318.
This is my address, please.
I will come
and give you the money back.
Someone, please help me!
-Sir, please help me.
-Hey.
Don't touch my bag.
Sir, please help me.
Ma'am.
My father is on the deathbed.
I must see him.
Please help me, ma'am!
Sir, I don't want to beg here!
But I need to be on that plane!
I need to see my father.
I need to go, sir.
I'm running out of time.
Somebody, please help me!
-My mother's old and alone!
-Come out, I say!
I must be on that plane.
My father is on the deathbed.
What's wrong?
-What's wrong?
-I don't know. Let me check.
SHRI RENUKA YALLAMMATALLI LORRY SERVICES
You're a bloody failure!
And will always be one!
Who is it?
You taught thousands to write
and you can barely scribble now!
The train has to stop here!
I can't open my eye, Maha!
You were his only child
and you couldn't even light his pyre!
Why did you come?
Why the hell did you come?
Why did you come
after everything's over?
This is all my fate!
He longed for you
until the very end!
Had you just seen him once
he would've gone peacefully!
He said you wouldn't want
to speak to a failure!
You deserted us
and walked away.
He waited until the end
for your return.
Let go of my feet!
-We both had such high hopes with you!
-Father.
The breath he held on to,
imagining you were back,
will never return!
He died waiting for you!
You bloody wretch!
-Those who are executed get one last wish.
-I didn't have enough money.
You deprived him of that, too!
You never understood him.
See it for yourself.
You can read, right? Read them.
Go ahead!
Read them all!
Today, my son left home.
Though obstacles be many,
he will overcome them all!
Take it!
Take it and read it!
This is what he scribbled
when he was dying!
"Parvathi says he'll fly.
But I know he won't rest
until he makes everyone fly with him."
He imagined you reaching great heights!
You broke his heart!
"They say a sparrow can never aspire
to fly high.
But my son will change that!"
He had so much faith in you.
You sinner! You failed to understand a man
who understood you so well!
He always said,
"Time is the most valuable asset".
If you can't reach in time,
what's the point of your love or money?
Why?
He was hard on you
only for your own good.
Was that wrong?
Is that why you punished him?
He didn't lose!
When you win,
it is his victory, too.
I'll never be angry again, Mother.
I'll never be angry again.
Next three years at the Air Force,
I had just one thought.
To make the common man fly.
Why go to the President for this?
I could've done this for you.
Anyway, all the best.
Move round and round
Like a surging hurricane!
Stomp over arrogance
Like a bull off its leash!
A streak like the lightning
Tear it all down
Punch it and spread to dry
Then, dust it off and toss it out
Mr. Balaiyya!
When aviation is so down,
you're expanding your airlines!
The new aviation minister says
he'll give no handouts.
-What do you think?
-Hey Trivedi!
One must take risks to win!
I need no handouts, chump!
My beer company's enough
to bail me out!
Hey, Paresh!
-What is this 'aero show'?
-A flight exhibition, uncle!
Like our town fair!
-Is our plane here?
-I'll bring them in from Malaysia!
We got our license!
-Let's go closer!
-When do our planes arrive?
It'll be here in a week, sir.
Paresh!
Expanding your flights, huh?
I can't take risks like you, my friend.
I came to check out turboprops
for cargo.
Our planes await us at Malaysia.
There's Paresh!
Why did Prakash Babu
bring that halfwit here?
Teacher and student.
Oh, so he's that guy!
He looks like a nice chap.
So obviously, he's doomed!
Let's sit back and enjoy it!
You know a bumble bee, Balaiyya?
It's not designed aerodynamically.
Yet, it flies!
Do you know why?
Because it doesn't know that
it can't fly!
Make sure he learns that now.
Baby, who is it?
Che says, "Call me".
-Our planes are leaving, Maha!-What?
PlaneAm canceled our deal!
They're taking their planes
in three days!
Why?
The Indian DGCA is asking them
for Boeing blueprints!
Hundreds of Boeings fly in India!
No one's asked them for blueprints!
They told us to check with the government!
PlaneAm's levied a fifty lakh fine
for blocking their flights!
Why is Indian DGCA targeting us?
Maha?
Pay up, sir!
I'll pay.
I'll take an auto rickshaw!
The new by-law was passed last week.
Didn't you know?
Will Boeing give their blueprints?
Will any company
reveal their trade secrets?
How can you change rules suddenly?
Calm down, Mr. Chandra Mahesh.
Laws can't be changed for you.
But you will, for the rich, right?
My money's gone.
That's not my problem.
It's your headache.
The DGCA has just done its job.
-Are you bloody screwing with me!
-Watch your words.
Why do you want
to start an airline?
-Go home and graze your cows!
-Mahesh!
Go pimp for Jaz Air!
I can break your damn neck!
But I'm being patient
and you keep fucking with me?
Let him go!
Listen to me!
-Prakash sir.
-Hey, Mahesh.
I've been trying for days
to see you!
They've changed the laws!
PlaneAm's ending the deal
and demanding a penalty!
We'll lose our planes!
If you could loan me fifty lakhs...
647.38 crores.
No, sir.
I only asked for fifty lakhs.
Six hundred and forty seven
point thirty eight crores.
Sir?
That's Mr. Paresh's income
from his travel agency alone
every year.
And you wanted him to join you
and destroy his own business.
He taught you a lesson.
You still don't get it?
Paresh is the main angel investor
of SCI.
Not just SCI, he also controls
people like me in it.
Prakash, come here.
While you came to me
asking for a few lakhs
look how easily he crushed you!
Yes, that's Paresh.
By the time you settle your debt,
you'll be finished.
But your idea?
Fantastic!
Never occurred to us!
Check that out!
Your PlaneAm aircraft.
Mahesh!
We can break and make laws in a day!
He spent just ten minutes
thinking about you
and you're finished!
Don't make him think anymore, my boy!
Good luck.
Paresh!
-Where the hell is Paresh?
-Oh, no.
Where is Paresh!
Bloody bastard!
Paresh!
Didn't I tell you he would ruin your life?
How can I relax
with you married to this nut?
Only God can save him now!
How long will he live off you?
Are you listening to me?
It's really shameful.
The cow's been mooing all day!
Go check, you moron!
You don't own a cow.
She means me, fool!
Here. I came to give you this.
An arrogant shrew
with a worthless husband.
Keep it.
Take her and leave.
Some daughter, she is. A witch!
Put the cake down.
What a loser husband. Let's go.
-Mom, the bags.
-Shut up and come!
You haven't eaten all day.
I didn't see you come in.
When did you come?
Maha, Seenu uncle
from next door came by.
His kids want to join a tutorial center
for IAS exams.
He feels you would teach them better.
What do you say?
They're smart kids.
It'll help you take your mind off this.
Uncle said he'd pay you.
I knew it.
I knew you would eventually get there.
Get where, Maha?
What is it now?
Pointing out I'm a freeloader, huh?
Did I say that?
How much did Seenu uncle offer
to help you out?
Your mom was right about you blabbing
when hungry.
Stop treating me like an idiot!
At least, your mom was direct!
Why are you fighting with me?
Let's figure out your next move.
Oh, yeah, must figure that out.
Gee, I wonder why that didn't occur
to this dimwit!
Enlighten me on how to run an airline,
baker girl.
Go ahead.
I'm all ears.
Every time you met investors
with your idea
they laughed at you, didn't they?
To them, your idea
was just a damn cupcake!
And what you demean
puts food on our table.
Despite my family's objections,
I married you.
I believed you'd make the poor fly!
Is it all just talk?
Are you going work
towards it at all!
Make it happen!
Don't mope around like a loser, Maha!
Why do you want to live with a loser?
Get lost!
Go away!
Achieve something and then get macho!
Fucking ego!
My love!
Love of my life!
Baby?
As darkness falls
My heart races
My eyes are exhausted
From seeking you far and wide
I yearn to be beside you
I dream of resting
On your shoulder
My heart calls out for you
Did Baby come here, Seby?
No, Maha.
Only you can take my breath away
And you know it too
My cursed hand
I raised against you...
O forgive me
My anger has faded away
Come back to me
Where will I go, Maha?
This is my home.
My only home.
My love
I looked for you everywhere.
I would have kept you running
for days
if I wasn't pregnant.
Who breaks such news in this way?
Can't you talk like a normal person?
I can't. This is who I am.
And only then,
it gets into your thick skull!
Baby!
To hell with the net...
Damn sparrows!
Why don't they eat?
The bigger birds will eat it all
and leave them hungry.
A sparrow is neither too big
nor flies too high.
And so needs very less food.
Baby!
-What is it, Maha?
-Come with me.
For its size
and the height it flies...
it doesn't need much food.
So...
Not much fuel.
Small planes!
Turboprops!
Baby!
Small planes need less fuel.
So tickets can be even cheaper.
I'll convert cargo planes
into passenger ones! A first in India!
Our turboprops are the best in the market.
But large planes have replaced turboprops
everywhere.
Your planes are used
only for cargo transport.
I'll turn your cargos into
passenger planes. Joint venture.
What is this 'tur-bur' you speak of?
Turboprops, uncle!
They're like the small Maruti 800 cars.
They only fly half as high as big planes.
Fuel cost also gets halved.
Won't they be cramped?
Yes, the planes are small.
But they will also get full
with just 70 people.
Large planes need 200 passengers
to get full.
Therefore, low costs and high profits.
You want us to give our planes to you
for free? Why should we?
7,500 trains operate in my country,
every day.
That's 25 million passengers a day.
Plus, there are several private
and government bus services.
If just two percent of these people
fly in our airline,
ours would be a profitable business.
Can't fly too far with turboprops, sir.
We can't do prestige routes
like Chennai to Delhi.
Must it be a non-stop to Delhi?
Make stops at Vijayawada and Nagpur
and voila!
We cover big cities and small towns.
That's the strength of a sparrow.
If we share costs with Turboprop company,
in a joint venture
four crores will suffice!
Tea bill of 200 bucks is still due.
It's about to rain millions
and you're asking for 200 bucks!
-Get lost!
-Yeah, right!
You can't even pay 200,
but dreaming of making crores!
I'll take these with me.
I listened to you
and set up shop here.
I was worried it wouldn't take off.
I expected 300-400 bucks tops,
but I make over a 1,000!
A thousand?
Per week?
No!
Per day!
The college girls across the road
come by every day
and the boys follow them in
like puppies.
My shop's in the right place.
Whose idea was that?
Shall we go?
Not bad, Maha.
I thought you were the only one
following girls to bakeries.
But most boys are, too.
Isn't it time for work?
Let's eat. I've ordered fritters.
I'm craving for one!
A coffee, bro.
Lots of sugar.
-No, thanks.
-What's wrong, Maha?
Paresh isn't in India this month.
We must bring in our planes secretively
before he's back.
How?
Ground work and feasibility reports
are done.
I even had a meeting
with a French company.
If we do this correctly,
we'll be up and running.
We don't even need eight crores.
Just four will do.
Why wait? Start.
We can!
But only after the company's registered,
can this take off.
Ba-Baby?
Can you lend me fifteen thousand?
Is that my coffee?
Lots of sugar?
-For registration...
-Give me the bill.
Just pay the registration fee.
I can finalize the deal.
This time, I'll succeed.
I'll repay you in three months.
I'll keep accounts.
You keep track of it, too.
Baby...
Good morning, sir.
Maha!
Never mind 15,000
I'll give you 20,000.
You talk of doing great things.
Act accordingly.
Why all this false pride with me?
Sorry.
What?
Why is it so hard
to ask your wife for help?
I've said this already!
My bakery is yours
and your planes are mine.
Isn't that our deal?
One tasty sweet for the boss lady.
Bhawar?
Hey!
-Yes, sir!
-How?
You're a goddamn pauper.
How can you sleep so peacefully?
Brother, come.
Something's not right.
Is there a problem?
Relax, Paresh. All is well.
Just a small glitch with turboprops.
We'll sort it tomorrow. Okay?
How many times have I told you?
Good news can wait.
But problems,
tell me right away.
The planes we wanted for cargo
have been taken by someone
as passenger planes.
Ask Mirza to talk.
And if they do not agree,
make them agree!
Isn't passenger transport
a better offer for them?
Pay them more than what we promised.
They're not interested.
Call Ananth.
It's 3 AM, Paresh!
So?
I'm awake! Why should he sleep?
What is this?
A joint venture
between Turboprop International
and NCS Aviation Private Limited.
Registered in the name
of Ms. Sundari.
With Turboprop in the forefront,
he stayed hidden and sealed the deal.
I signed
without a second thought as
only you've been dealing
with turboprops.
I'm sorry!
Don't worry, Paresh.
He's not rich like Balaiyya.
He's just a fool.
He'll run away
with his tail between his legs.
Balaiyya's the fool.
Once his father's wealth is gone,
he'll disappear.
Call up whoever, wherever
but finish him.
Don't be hasty, Paresh.
The CBI's still investigating
what we did last time.
I don't care!
His plane must not land here.
Okay?
Okay.
Damn villager!
Yes. That's what he is.
Not him, me.
India must only speak
of my story from rags to riches!
There has to be only one Paresh.
Right?
No one knows you here,
buddy!
But everyone seems to know the witch!
-How are you?
-I'm good!
How are you, brother?
I was just praising you.
-Take care of the bakery, uncle!
-Sure.
Mock me all you want.
I'll still cook a feast for you.
-Please come!
-Sure!
My sister's getting married
on the 15th.
Just a minute.
-Come here.
-Next month?
-You can go.
-What's up?
Money's the problem, right?
Yes. Why?
Don't worry.
That's no problem at all.
Who much?
I meant 'how much' in English?
It's okay.
I can handle it.
Why do you hesitate to ask me?
Just a minute.
Here you go.
Take it, son.
What's the matter?
11,528 rupees!
My life savings.
Take it all and get things going.
Happy?
Don't tell Baby about this.
She'll rip me apart.
-God damn, uncle...
-Quit laughing!
It's for all of you.
Split it up equally.
We need three crores
and twenty five lakhs.
About 2,000 times what you've given us.
Three crores?
I don't even know how many zeroes
it has!
This is all I have.
Please don't mistake me.
Won't this do?
It's not that, Uncle.
Uncle!
Your heart's much bigger
than a mere three crores!
Keep it safe.
I don't have much...
-Forget about it.
-Uncle is so generous.
Come in.
Good morning.
As a bank manager, I should've called
the income tax department first.
Sir.
How much, sir?
See!
One and a half lakhs. Twenty thousand.
One lakh. Ten thousand. Five hundred.
Your account's been receiving
deposits all day from Tsundur!
-Can I make a call?
-Yeah. Sure.
Tsundur Post?
Mahesh's on the line.
I sent two lakhs to your account.
Did you get it?
Munnuswamy...
How did you raise so much?
I pledged my land to Ravi.
Give me the phone.
I postponed my sister's wedding a bit!
The groom will wait
until you repay.
You keep going.
You should've told me.
Why did you go to that bloodsucking Ravi?
We can't be bystanders
and see you work hard
to make our lives better.
It's because you stopped the train,
our land prices have skyrocketed.
-Let me speak to Mahesh!
-Go on!
I sold all my paddy and sent
eight thousand rupees. Did you get it?
-Hold on!
-I did.
-Yes, he got it.
-Give it to him.
-Here you go.
-Pipe down.
Maha, my boy...
Grandpa...
I just planted chilies
as there were no rains.
I could only send 500 rupees.
Did you get it?
You're struggling without rain.
Why all this?
This kid wants to talk to you!
Talk to him. Here you go.
-Hello?
-Talk to him.
How are you, uncle?
Did you get my money?
How did you get so much?
From my piggy bank.
Take me in your airplanes, too.
The neighboring towns have donated.
Make your donations right away, residents.
Stand in line.
Don't cut in.
Thirty seven thousand. Twelve thousand.
Forty thousand. Thirty one thousand.
Look properly. It's thirty-one lakhs.
Thirty-one lakhs?
Get the airplanes here real soon, my boy!
I will fly all our people
to my daughter's wedding.
No, sir.
Let's first get back your lands from Ravi.
I'll come talk to him myself.
Maha...
Mom?
If you're the teacher's son,
I'm his wife!
I demanded the documents back
from Ravi.
He told us to pay up
six months' interest anyway.
No one can touch us
if we're united.
Victory or defeat,
it's all in your hands now.
You'll win, right?
Your father's always with you.
We're all praying for you, son.
Win!
We're counting on you.
Victory is yours.
-Shall I hang up?
-Okay, Mom.
All major airports
are under Paresh's control.
-You'll land your plane on this airstrip?
-Yes.
Built in the British era.
Airstrips for postal delivery
and diplomatic trips.
People like Nehru have been here.
Abandoned unused airstrips?
How many? Three or four?
500!
500 of these exist across India.
We'll prep them for our planes to land!
Spark the coal
Which lies within your core!
Light up your future
With the flames that abound
Ignore the tornadoes
That stand in your way
Move forward
And fulfill your dreams
The unworthy will taunt you
Unaware of your worth
Emerge as a diamond
And they'll shut their wagging tongues
The unworthy will taunt you
Unaware of your worth
Emerge as a diamond
And they'll shut their wagging tongues
Tear to shreds, all that obstructs
Give wings to dreams that trust in you
And soar
What are you saying, Seby?
Be clear.
For the first time, Indians can book
plane tickets with credit cards.
How many Indians have credit cards?
They all have telephones, right?
That is enough!
They can call our call center
and book tickets.
With a PNR number, they pick up tickets
at their bank or supermarket.
But...
We are trying this
with publicly owned computers.
Interworld spends six months
just testing this software!
-Yeah.
-We don't have that kind of luxury.
No one else has tried this here.
This will be the first time in India.
You want to sell your tickets
at the railway counter?
Why will I agree to take away
my business?
Every day, there are 10,000 people
in the waiting list for A/C coaches.
I'll take only those people in my airline.
Just give me a small space
next to your reservation counter.
Bottom line is,
they need to travel, right?
Okay. It's a great idea!
All the very best, Mr. Mahesh.
Why should victory reach you
When you summon it with a snap?
How will one understand the difference
Between you and anyone else?
You need a story, too
Narrate it with pride
The sweat of your effort
Shall bloom with the fragrance of victory
Our eyes may be small
But not our dreams
Let not your limitations
Draw your boundaries
BISMI MOBILES
SALES & SERVICES
We won't be born again
After we're one with the earth
-A call for you.
-What is it called?
The company's called Deccan Air.
Do you like it?
-He isn't fit.
-Is he?
You bugger off.
You come in!
Write a brand new story,
as your life changes today!
Deccan Air won't get pilots.
We paid them three times more
than he did.
They took it!
Dismiss all of them next month.
Brother?
If I can buy them,
anybody can buy them.
-Stop it!
-Maha's here!
The pilots didn't show up!
-Seby!
-Where's he off to?
-Wait, I'll tell you!
-Do you get anything he does?
Where are you going?
None of our pilots came!
A guy who can buy a government
can buy anyone.
There are our pilots.
Retired military aviators
who flew fighter jets for India.
Retired Pilots?
There is an age limit!
Let me in on the joke!
Air Force pilots retire at 57.
Civilian pilots at 61.
They can fly for another four years!
Kickass!
Two can play this game!
You've upheld Guntur's pride!
Captain Rajiv Manohar,
coordinated all this.
Retired as Air Commodore.
I don't believe this.
Is this how it is done!
-We need to focus on the airline, uncle!
-Yes, yes!
-I've been waiting for you.
-Bored at work?
I have a proposal for you.
What proposal?
A business proposal!
What business?
Do you do this to all your vendors?
Let my catering division
take care of your in-flight snacks.
Logistically impossible
with just one outlet in Madras.
It is possible!
Who told you Madras was my only base?
I have franchises!
Che's family in Vijayawada.
My brother in Vizakh.
Projected monthly turnover's ten lakhs!
That's 1.2 crores per year!
Welcome to Deccan Air,
Mrs. Sundari Kanayanam!
Don't expect any special treatment.
Alright?
You too, don't expect any discounts.
Deal.
We're talking business!
Business is done, right?
It's coming!
What's this?
I don't get it!
Like we get anything you say!
When our planes land
for the first time
it would be auspicious
to land facing east!
You won't get it!
Back off!
No! They'll land
only as per the designated coordinates!
There you go again!
Never clear!
That's ours, right?
Look, uncle!
Our plane's coming!
Chennai Tower, this is Deccan Air 582.
Minimum fuel.
Requesting landing clearance.
Go around, Deccan Air 582.
Where are the other two planes?
Is that why you brought three garlands?
Others will be here in two days.
Why aren't they landing?
They are not getting permission to land?
Is there a problem with
DA-582's landing?
It's huge!
Garlands are small, damn!
How long will they circle around?
Get to the ATC, boys!
I'll handle the ground operation!
-Seby, come with me.
-Go!
-I need to go too, uncle!
-Where are you going?
-Let go! Why is he running?
-Don't run!
I said we have a fuel emergency,
goddammit!
I say again.
Deccan Air 582. Go around.
There is something's wrong, Captain.
They're ignoring protocol.
Chennai Tower,
requesting reason for denial!
I say this again.
Go around, Deccan Air 582!
Paresh.
This is highly risky.
If we delay any further,
the plane is going to crash.
You said you just wanted to scare them!
You're using civil aviation property!
I'll be the one investigated!
How dare you?
You are not dumb enough
to piss off the man who put you
in the DGCA.
Right?
You owe me, my friend!
Paresh, we'll be in trouble,
if this flight crashes.
Che!
Tambaram Air Force.
Runway 1-5.
Land there!
Do you have enough fuel for that?
I'll take care of it.
Switch to company frequency!
Who do you think you are?
I own that fucking plane!
Guards, take him out.
Security breach at gate one!
Che, listen, if the fuel is low,
switch to auxiliary engines!
Don't teach me how to do my job!
My dad warned me not to hang out with you.
I should've listened!
Anything happens to me,
tell Preethi I love her.
I'll tell that Brigadier's daughter, too!
Get our plane home safe, man!
Che!
Come in, Che!
Get help!
-Open the emergency hatch! Hurry!
-He's fine, right?
We are ex Air Force!
There are two pilots inside!
They need some help!
Batch of '87!
We need some help!
Two pilots are trapped inside!
Please help them.
Please help them!
It's an emergency!
Che!
Are you okay?
Jai Hind, sir!
Why didn't you declare Mayday
and land at the Airport?
If we had, they would've impounded
my flights for months!
My launch is on August 25th.
And it must happen!
Excuse me, sir.
Jai Hind, sir.
Call for you, sir.
The airport authorities want an update
for the press!
Three years ago, a Saudia Air Boeing
made an emergency landing.
On this very airstrip!
-Remember, Chaitanya?
-Sir.
What did we do?
We investigated for terrorist links.
And then we levied a five crore fine.
You three will get a ten-year prison term
along with the fine.
You haven't even taken off
and you already have enemies
all the way to Delhi!
We're done here.
They aren't terrorists!
Tell them
I'm letting them go!
They'll pay a fine!
-Dismiss!
-Jai Hind, sir!
You will pay a fine!
For the unauthorized landing
at our base
it's 25,000!
You can pay three months after
you start your airline.
What are you waiting for?
A hug and a sendoff ceremony?
Go.
-Out!
-Sir!
They'll target you for letting me go.
Do I look scared?
You've never liked me, sir.
Maha!
If I had not punished you
back then
my cadets wouldn't have respected me.
And if I bow to political pressure now
I won't respect myself.
Brother...
What you intend to do
is much bigger
than either of our egos.
A soldier must ensure
to bring every trooper home.
Like you did today.
You are a leader today.
Leader.
I don't smoke.
You shouldn't either.
You're getting old, right?
Hey!
Don't you dare call me old!
Get out before I change my mind.
Get lost!
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Mahesh!
Ready to fly, huh?
Are you inviting the minister?
Good, good!
Need a recommendation?
Do you know Tata?
Ratan Tata?
He himself couldn't start an airline here.
Poor guy tried for 20 years!
-Twenty years...
-You think you can scare me?
Going on and on
about Ratan Tata!
I'm not Ratan Tata!
You bloody...
People trust me.
That will do.
Ah, the crowds!
Public opinion?
That changes every week!
Be careful, Mr. Mahesh.
Excuse me.
I have an airline to run, my friend.
It's my time now!
The people are with him.
You keep swatting at that bee,
but it keeps flying.
Murthy?
-Murthy!
-Sir.
It's Mallesham, sir.
Right, Mallesham!
Mallesham...
Do you know Chandra Mahesh Kanayanam?
I do, sir.
What do you know?
I heard he's offering
plane tickets at low price.
You'll make people fly
for just one rupee?
Impossible!
Today, 75% of flights fly half-empty!
I'll charge a rupee
for each empty seat.
Just a rupee for those who book
much in advance.
Once those are booked,
500 rupee seats open up!
Then, the 1,000s!
But aren't you deceiving people
by giving just ten one rupee tickets?
Three planes.
Ten trips each per day.
That is 300 people will fly at one rupee,
per day.
And even our most expensive ticket
costs the same as an A/C train ticket.
Will you fly in that plane?
I don't know if I will, sir.
But I want my mother to fly
at least once.
She'll be very happy.
There are two unused airstrips
in your region.
Imagine the impact
when these planes land there!
So my servant will fly with me
as an equal?
And I'm supposed to let that happen?
His investment.
That must be destroyed first.
We're proud to cover
the launch of this airline
that could be a significant milestone
in the history of Indian aviation!
Even a cup of tea costs more than a rupee.
But Maha's making people fly for a rupee!
I hereby announce two airstrips
will be operated in my region alone!
I've always been a visionary.
We must encourage the youth of our nation.
I hereby declare Deccan Air launched!
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls,
you're welcome onboard,
Deccan Air maiden flight.
We're now ready for departure.
Enjoy our services. Thank you.
Deccan Air 582
ready for departure.
Line up and clear for take-off.
Wind calm.
-Fire! Get up!
-Go! Go!
Please sit!
What's going on?
Look!
Please sit down!
There's smoke in engine one!
Stay calm!
Mahesh, where are you going?
Please stay calm!
Captain!
Captain, smoke.
Captain, smoke.!
Abort!
Captain! Captain!
Reject take-off!
Power lever idle! Shut down engines!
Captain, come on!
Apply brakes, Captain!
Applying maximum brakes!
Deccan Air 582 to Chennai Tower!
Mayday, Mayday! Engine is smoking!
Evacuate! Evacuate! Evacuate!
Evacuate! Go! Go!
Come along, sir!
Mahesh, what is this?
Steer clear of the aircraft!
Stay back!
Move away! Sir!
Relax, sir. Please wait in the lounge.
I'll set things right.
How much longer, Che?
Forty five minutes!
Just give me some time.
Sir, relax. Nothing to panic, sir.
This is a failure, man!
Drive!
-Sir! Please don't say that!
-Drive!
Sir!
Please, sir!
His problem is he aims too high!
Rush into things, and this happens!
You put our village to shame!
-Shut up, dad!
-You shut up!
Guys! Guys!
Mahesh is here.
Come on, come on.
Mr. Mahesh, is it true
you disregarded safety regulations?
Answer us!
Your very first trip ended in disaster!
Your cheap tickets
will claim lives!
It was not intentional!
-Did you not follow safety regulations?
-We have!
Answer us, sir!
People deserve the truth!
-Why have you gone silent?
-Answer us!
Speak up!
Is human life worth so little to you?
Is a life worth so little?
I'm explaining that.
I'll handle this!
You handle them!
Let's go, uncle!
Come along, uncle!
We can go.
Is it true you did not follow
safety regulations? Answer us!
As per international regulations,
we did safety checks in India and France!
Our goal was low-priced airlines.
Not undermining security.
India has so many basic issues!
Is flying a necessity?
Every benefit must reach everyone!
And they will!
This is my domain.
And I want to break the barriers here!
Is it wrong?
Such philosophies only sound good.
I am telling you!
Hear me out!
We did all due diligence!
No rules were violated!
People are not about to get into
one of these flights in a hurry.
People will not fly Deccan Air again.
This may well be their last flight.
The teacher is back!
Are we contesting elections?
Good enough if people fly.
So shall we issue a CRS?
Yeah. Go check!
Has the oil been uplifted, Che?
They've assigned Bay 64 to us.
Mr. Rajiv Manohar,
your statement says that
Deccan Air violated many safety rules.
Can you elaborate?
What crimes did Deccan Air commit?
Tell us.
Is it true that Deccan Air
was indifferent?
No, sir.
This is all my fault.
What's this, sir?
He keeps changing his statement!
Did someone force you
to sabotage Deccan Air's flight?
I was negligent during fueling.
I didn't do my safety checks properly.
It's my fault.
Is someone threatening you?
We all know who is threatening whom.
Explain that, Mr. Manohar.
Who is threatening you?
Let it go.
I'm satisfied with his statement.
It's okay.
Deccan Air's not at fault.
File the report as 'Pilot Negligence'.
It was not a technical failure.
Deccan Air is cleared of all charges.
I trusted you, Captain.
I have many problems at home.
Worse than mine?
They'll try to buy us, sir.
Saying no is our only strength!
But I...
I won't ask you to leave.
What are you doing, Maha?
Why did you let him off?
He's my father's age, Che.
Monday 9 pm, an exclusive interview
with Paresh Goswami!
-Live!
-Maha?
Why won't you pick up the phone
or charge the damn thing?
Balaiyya PA trying to contact you.
They want to meet you tomorrow!
I'm not going.
It could be useful to us.
I don't want his help!
The shape we're in,
we need all the help we can get!
I'll not deal with his kind anymore.
I'm taking the evening bus home.
You just got here this morning.
Stay here for a couple of days.
No, buddy,
I just came by to see you.
My sister's fiance's family
is asking for a wedding date.
Don't stress.
Whenever you say!
Just indicate a date,
and I'll manage the rest.
See you.
Bye, Baby!
Let's go, Raja.
Not one interview of yours
is here.
The future of Deccan Air
remains a question mark.
Running an airline is not a game!
No wonder it tanked!
Airplanes are for the rich!
Not for people like us!
Paresh Goswami questions
if the DGCA enquiry commission was bribed.
Even our advertisement's been buried!
They play with our feelings
and royally screw us!
Due to safety issues,
Deccan Air has come to an end.
They broke people's faith in us.
A plane, Maha!
Come on, race!
Maha?
Welcome, welcome.
Come have a drink.
No, we're good.
Go ahead, have a drink, man.
Have fun!
-Why did you call?
-Alright, I'll get to the point.
Why do we need two airlines?
I'll merge your company with mine.
Who will fly in our planes then?
Of course, only the rich!
My team said a maximum of 12 crores.
But I'll give you 15!
Guys! Do we have a deal?
Okay. Sixteen crores, then!
Mahesh, you better take it
before I change my mind.
Sir, give us two minutes.
We'll discuss and get back to you.
Okay.
Let's think it over, Maha.
I already have.
No.
Why are you taking a risk?
It's a great offer.
Take it, man!
Sometimes, I get doubts
about my airline's success.
But the way you're lusting after it
my doubts are all gone.
Come on. You've no business sense.
You can't survive a day here
without my support.
I don't get you, man!
You won't.
You're a socialite.
I'm a socialist.
We are nothing alike.
Imbecile!
Let's go!
-Did he call me an imbecile?
-Yes, sir.
How can you decide alone?
Don't you need to discuss it with us?
I quit my job because of you!
Is that nothing to you?
You call this a partnership?
You'll bring us to the streets?
What's your problem?
Tell me!
You're crazy!
Think about us too.
We all are in deep shit.
Seby has a family to feed!
My dad cut me off when I quit my job!
Aren't we human beings too!
Who can stick with you?
Is your wife happy at least?
-Hey.
-Hey, hey!
What are you doing?
Go on, hit me!
Don't hit the bellies of the villagers
relying on you!
Am I? That dog inside doesn't get it!
Don't you, too?
By turning him down,
we make a billion Indians fly one day!
Why are we here?
Do you get
what is he asking us to sell?
Our dream.
Don't you get that?
How much did he offer?
Sixteen crores.
Did you take it?
I let down our family, Baby.
Did you poison the food?
I would have, if you sold out.
This is a small show
on All India Radio.
It will do, ma'am.
It's the language of my people.
I'll talk to the new FM stations.
They're growing.
You'll get a wider reach.
Ready?
Five, four, three, two, one.
Go!
Sir?
We look at the skies
with awe,
but wouldn't dare dream
of seeing the world from up there.
Same thing back home.
But today, we've risen too
and come to fly.
Goswami's afraid of sub-standard people
entering the industry.
Yes.
He is terrified of us.
But, not for the reasons he claims.
He knows well that our airline
passed every safety test like his.
So, what does he fear?
He fears that those beneath him
will rise to his level.
The rich want the poor to remain poor.
A century ago, they claimed
electricity was only for them.
Fifty years ago,
they said that about cars.
Who are they to decide?
No one except them
should enjoy it all, right?
We spend days
to go from place to place.
But the rich?
They fly like Gods above us!
If we level with them,
no one will be beneath them.
That's what he fears!
You can now book plane tickets
over the phone.
We will give you a PNR number.
Just show the number
at your bank or post office.
Why do small towns remain small?
Why haven't they grown?
To grow,
sometimes we must walk
sometimes, we must run
and sometimes, we have to fly!
That is called as air connectivity.
My airline promises
air connectivity to everyone.
Our planes will reach
every small town!
And every place will grow!
Won't that scare the privileged?
The Question with Amit Trivedi.
-Thank you for joining us on The Question.
-Thank you.
Let's talk about what's on
everyone's mind: Low cost aviation.
Your thoughts, sir?
Look, Mr. Amit.
When flying in an aluminum can
at 1,000 km/hr,
what will be on your mind?
-Safety.
-Exactly!
That safety requires
all kinds of testing and security!
It's expensive,
but is a must!
When someone offers to lower that price,
people must think hard.
They have a point, sir.
How can one feel safe
at such low prices?
I have a question
for Goswami on safety.
His first class tickets
cost three times more than economy.
Should there be an accident
would he guarantee thrice the safety
to first class passengers?
But I will guarantee you this.
The Deccan Air pilots
flew fighter jets for India.
Who can fly you safer than them?
Here's why we are afraid
of Chandra Mahesh entering our business.
Shoddy equipment.
Retired pilots.
Sub-standard products.
He brings in many dangers.
The enquiry commission
cleared us of all charges.
I have no money
to bribe them.
I won't pay bribes
with my people's hard earned money.
If money was my priority,
I'd have made millions ages ago!
Or I'd gladly tend to my home
and child.
Because my wife's very successful.
You talk of so many obstacles.
Why do you go on?
My father wanted electricity
in our village. We got it.
He wanted a train for us.
We got it.
I want the benefits of modern science
to reach everyone.
I want to break the cost barrier
and the damn caste barrier too!
That's why our tickets
cost one rupee.
With quality and safety.
When flying on a legacy airline
like Jaz
you're completely assured
of safety.
As we have a well-trained crew
and the best infrastructure
our ticket prices
will be higher!
But...
Mahesh's stripping away all this
and offering dirt cheap tickets!
Tell me,
is your life worth
the same as a cup of tea?
My flights are safe.
All I'll say to those who don't trust
our safety report is this.
This is my own safety test!
The three people I love the most
will be on Deccan's first flights.
My mother Parvathi.
My wife Sundari.
My daughter Ammu.
Giving airlines to such people
is akin to giving guns
to the mentally ill!
This must be nipped in the bud!
It's a scary prospect!
Listen to him some more
and even I'll believe him!
Do you have any proof
for those acquisitions?
Maha! Maha!
-Maha!
Maha, hold on!
We've been trying to reach you!
What happened?
My cell battery's also dead, I guess.
You've not slept in three days.
You'll go crazy this way.
How can I sleep?
He could do anything to our planes.
We need to guard them.
Maha!
What's up, Chandra Mahesh?
Only Goswami has friends or what?
Don't we have friends?
We never let down our comrades!
Go and take rest, man!
I have this covered!
Get into position, boys!
Sir.
Take care of the wing tip clearance,
Mohan!
All in position at Bay 63?
...traveling flight DA 581,
please proceed to gate number two.
-Are we ready for boarding?
-Yes, Captain.
Okay.
Luggage tractors can go there,
right?
Welcome, Captain.
Welcome.
Just a minute, Raghava.
It's faster to get to my hometown by bus!
Why is only our plane parked so far away?
No matter where they throw us,
we will fly.
-Go on.
-Good day, ma'am. Sir.
We're really happy
to have you on board, ma'am.
-There are no passengers?
-There's still time, ma'am.
They'll come, won't they?
They will.
This is the last and final call
for passengers traveling
from Chennai to Thoothukudi
on flight DA-581,
which is set to take off in a few minutes.
I repeat, this is the last and final call
for passengers traveling to Thoothukudi
on flight DA 581.
Cheer up!
We'll handle it!
It's doubtful if people
will risk their lives and fly Deccan Air.
People will reject
such an unsafe airline.
And yes, it does look like the end
for Deccan Air.
Our flight's been cancelled,
Captain.
People didn't believe me, Baby.
Let's go.
Airplanes are for the rich!
Not for people like us!
They play with our feelings
and royally screw us!
You're out of your league!
Go home and graze your cows!
Giving airlines to such people
is akin to giving guns
to the mentally ill!
Wow! He remembers their plight!
Thought you forgot
as you were busy reproducing!
We are all praying for you, my son!
You should win!
We are all counting on you.
He spent just ten minutes
thinking about you
and you're finished!
Maha!
I'm sorry, Maha!
I screwed up!
You trusted me!
-Forget it!
-I messed up!
We tried.
That's what matters.
We came so close and screwed up!
I fucked up the Chennai booking!
What are you saying?
Be clear!
The Chennai flight tickets
were not confirmed from our end!
All bookings in our software
rolled back and got cancelled.
That's why none of our passengers came,
despite booking tickets!
Maha!
They were unable
to board our flight!
The problem was in the software!
People didn't lose faith in us!
Thousands of our tickets were sold!
People believed us!
The other two flights...
They were fully booked!
They flew at full capacity!
We won, Maha!
Your love brought the skies
Within our grasp
This will live on
Even when time is gone!
In the desert in our eyes
We wished for a few raindrops
Now, with your downpour
Our village smiles lush green
Super, bro!
The saplings in the soil
In an attempt to touch the sky
Suddenly take flight
Soaring towards the stars
In this scorching summer
As the full moon sheds coolness
Our hearts feel festive
Maha, my boy...
I'm so happy to have flown
in your plane today!
I've dreamt for years to fly.
Even my son couldn't
make it happen.
But today,
with my own savings
I flew all the way here!
How about that!
See you, son.
Let's go!
Buddy!
Now, with your downpour,
our village smiles lush green!
As mother fed her little girl
Plate in hand
She pointed to the faraway moon
Now, thanks to you, the time has come
To ascend a ladder to the sky
There are no stops
How was it?
In the path you tread!
There are no stops
"Parvathi says he will fly."
"But I know he won't rest
until he makes everyone fly with him!"
My darling!
You did it!
My dear boy!
You won!
Bless you, my boy!
Hello.
It's for you.
Watch what you say.
Hello?
Congratulations, Mr. Mahesh!
Can we meet?
I have a business proposal for you.
I was expecting your call,
Mr. Goswami.
Good, good, good.
I'll have my secretary fix an appointment.
Okay?
Who are you to give me an appointment?
What?
It doesn't matter whether I'm around
or you try to stop me.
The farmer has flown
and will continue to fly.
You don't own the sky, you scum.
-Mr. Mahesh?
-Now fuck off!
Lay a hand on me if you dare
Silence will resound
You'll be crushed under the heels
Of a fierce horse!
Transformed, have my ways of hunting
Lay a hand on me if you dare
What is it?
You messing with me, you hag?
What do you want?
Want to fly for a buck, huh?
Forget the plane, buddy!
The cakes which they provided!
So damn delicious!
I'll fly over and over
just for these cakes!
Hey bunface...
Whose idea was it?
Spark the coal
Which lies within your core
It's such a pleasure to meet up with you!
Drop the act!
How dare you sabotage the plane I was in.
Let's see how your planes are gonna fly!
-Sir, please let me explain!
-Sir, please come out!
The unworthy will taunt you
Unaware of your worth
Emerge as a diamond
And they'll shut their wagging tongues
The unworthy will taunt you
Unaware of your worth
First time flyer?
Nah! I've flown these things in circles!
It's okay.
Yeah, first time.
Give wings to dreams
That trust in you and soar
The sky is the limit
Let this chance not pass you by
-What do you do?
-I run a grooming establishment.
-Meaning?
-I cut hair in my village.
-I see...
-Own business!
-And you?
-I run a business, too!
Don't you recognize him?
He has a huge clothing store
in Bejawada!
He gave thirty one lakhs
to our fund for Mahesh! A big man!
There's no difference between us anymore!
He's broken down all that
and made us fly together!
Maha...
Did that girl fly the plane?
To hell with business class!
Tear it apart!
They paid for it.
They can sit wherever they please!
Let not your limitations
Draw your boundaries
Why the hurry to pay me back?
You'll need more
as you're growing.
Feel free to ask anytime!
We should make a film about you
and run it here!
He thinks this shack
is an IMAX theatre!
Let's go, Maha.
This guy thinks he's Director Mani Ratnam!
Write a brand new story
As your life changes today